tebrowser.com 2013-05-17

# TEBrowser 2.0 by Webily

TEBrowser.com ("TE Browser" and "TEBrowser" and "Webily, Ltd" and "Webily" and "us" and "we" and "our") has as its mission, the establishing of trusting relationships based on respect for your ("you" and "user" and "Customer" and "Accountholder") personal identity and information by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the site http://www.TEBrowser.com, all pages with that are an extension of the site, and every site and page that contains a Copyright notice designating the intellectual property rights of; "Webily, Ltd". Because TEBrowser demonstrates its commitment to our users’ privacy, we disclose TEBrowser's information practices herein and review our privacy practices for compliance from time to time.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy statement, please contact TEBrowser via the "Contact Us" link provided on every TEBrowser.com page.

### Information Collection and Use

### 1\. Information Collection

**1.a** Webily, Ltd is the sole owner of the information collected on http://www.TEBrowser.com. Webily, Ltd collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

### 2\. Registrations

**2.a** In order to use certain portions of our Web site, or to subscribe to our Services, a user must complete a registration form. During registration, a user is required to provide certain contact information (such as name, E-mail address, etc.). We use the information you supply to register you for use of our services and to contact you about services on our Web site for which you have expressed interest. If you encounter a form that contains a field requesting you to provide personal information (such as income level, gender, etc.), it is always "optional", however, its encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our Web sites.

### 3\. Customer Orders

**3.a** We require certain information from our Customers. Our Customers are asked to provide basic contact information (such as name, E-mail address, phone number, etc.), and financial information (such as a PayPal account email address) that is collected for use in our payment systems. No detailed payment information is collected or used for billing purposes to fill a Customer’s order through our payment systems, and is not collected directly by, or available to, Webily, Ltd employees. If there is trouble processing an order, the basic information we gather is used to contact the user, or to supply our payment system processor with information so they may contact you to resolve issues if you have contacted us to do so.

### 4\. Information Use

**4.a** Webily, Ltd may use demographic and survey data (such as job title, country, state/province, user interests, etc.) to learn more about the people and organizations that are interested in Webily's products and services to better focus our marketing efforts and to improve our product and service offerings. We may share this type of generic aggregated demographic information with an outside third party simply to showcase the level of interest individuals have in Webily's products and services, but at no time is any personal information or personal contact information given to or shared with any third party.

### 5\. User Profiles

**5.a** We store information that we collect through the forms you submit on our Web site(s) to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences, the products and services subscribed to, and history of payments. Consequently, collected information is tied to a users personally identifiable information to provide support, improve the content of our Web site(s) for the user, tailor a user’s visit to our Web site(s), and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them if they have requested it. We do not share your profile with third parties.

### 6\. Cookies

**6.a** A cookie is a piece of data stored on the hard drive of a user’s computer to tie information to or about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while you are on our Web site(s).

There are two primary kinds of cookies;  
**Session ID cookies:** The session ID cookie does **not** stay on a user's Computer, it is for the purpose of helping a user save time only. Once users close the browser window where they are engaged with a session ID cookie, the cookie simply terminates, it is not stored on the user's hard drive.  
**Persistent cookies:** A persistent cookie **does** stay on a user's Computer after they leave a Web site. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Generally, when people make comment to the effect that they "do not like cookies", this is the type of cookie they are referring to. Persistent cookies have a tendency to build up on a user's hard drive, and can force or limit the interaction when a user revisits a Web site. A user can easily remove persistent cookies by following Internet browser help file directions.

**6.b** Like any Web site with a password protected or "login" area, Webily does use "session ID" cookies, but we do not use the more obtrusive "persistent" cookies. Webily believes everyone should have a choice of the information gathered about them when visiting a Web site, thus we use forms that you know you are filling in to provide tracking of your interaction while visiting our Web site(s). We do not use any stealthy avenue to collect information about you without your knowledge in any way, or at any time.

**6.c** Recognizing session ID cookies is a function of your computer's operating system that automatically sets so you do not have to login a password more than once, thereby saving you time while visiting Web sites. Session ID cookies are activated by your Computer's operating system because it remembers that you have an area that you login to while visiting our Web site. If a user has their system configured to reject all cookies, they may still access and use our Web site(s), but could have to manually type in their passwords every time they enter into a password protected area depending on how they have their settings configured.

**6.d** Some third party Web sites you reach through our Web site(s) may use persistent cookies (for example, advertisers), however, once you leave our Web site(s), we have no access to, nor do we have any control over, cookies you may encounter.

### 7\. Third Party Advertising

**7.a** We do not use a third party Advertising Agency for ad content on any of our Web site(s). Information about visits to any of our Web sites, such as number of times an ad is viewed, is logged to be used to serve ads to users on our Web sites, but we do not log a user's name, address, or other personal information when visiting an ad. For more information about how your information is logged on other Web sites we link to, and the advertising you visit and their use of cookies there, please check the privacy statement on their Web site(s). Our privacy policies cover the use of cookies by Webily only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers you may encounter on a Web site we may link to.

**7.b** You can identify when you are visiting one of our Web sites by "Webily, Ltd." being a part of the copyright notice at the bottom of every page we control and own.

### 8\. Log Files

**8.a** Like most standard Web site servers, we use log files. Log files include generic information like internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, Internet service providers (ISPs), referring/exit pages, platform types, date/time stamping, and the number of clicks and what is clicked on our Web site(s) to analyze trends, administer the site, analyze traffic movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, referring pages, date/time stamping, etc. are not linked to any personally identifiable information unless a form is filled in by the user. When this type of information is logged, it is done for our protection and the protection of our Customers and Program Members as proof that a user has requested information. This is otherwise known as "opt-in" information, or a user "opting-in" to receive information from Webily(like our Newsletters, product information, etc.), or to provide an avenue to protect our Program Members from fictitious or false complaints (i.e. Spam complaints) when the user has in fact requested more information.

**8.b** In the event a user does opt-in to receive more information, material they receive from Webily will always have an easy means of being removed from receiving further material. If material is delivered to you from one of our Program Members, and you do not see an easy form of removal from receiving future material from them, simply reply to the Member requesting removal. If you have requested removal from receiving material from a Program Member, and they are not respecting your right to privacy by continuing to send you more material past seventy-two (72) hours, we want to know about it so we can resolve the matter as quickly as possible. If you feel your right to privacy is being violated, you may file a detailed complaint as directed at our "Anti-Spam Policy", Article 7.

### 9\. Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

**9.a** Although Webily does not use them on our Web site(s), because we link to other Web sites, that may not be under our control, we feel you should be aware that some companies, usually advertising companies, may employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs) that helps them better manage content on a Web site by informing them what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the on-line movements of Web users. The main difference between the two is that clear gifs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear gifs are not tied to a user's personally identifiable information. Clear Gifs can work "with" existing cookies on a computer if they are both from the same Web site or advertising company. That means, for example, that if a person visited “www.XYZ-Company”, which uses an advertising company's clear gif, the Web site would match the clear gif's identifier and the advertising company's cookie ID number, to show the past on-line behavior for that computer. This collected information would then either be given to the advertising company, or collected by the advertising company directly.

**9.b** Webily may use clear gifs in our HTML-based E-mails, but this is done simply to let us know what E-mail(s) we send have been opened by the recipients, and does not track where you go or what Web sites you visit while surfing the Internet. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness, or the lack thereto, of our marketing campaigns. E-mail(s) sent out in plain text format do not carry clear gifs. If a user receiving E-mail from Webily would like to opt-out, they may do so at any time. Please see the "Choice/Opt-out", Article 13, below for more information about opting-out from E-mailings.

### 10\. Communications from Webily

**10.a Special Offers and Updates**  
We send all new Customers an activation E-mail to supply verification of the Customer's E-mail address and enable password access to the Customer's account. Established Customers will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and our company newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users' we present the option to not receive these types of communications.

**10.b Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and E-mail address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the "Choice/Opt-out", Article 13, below for more information about being removed from our E-mailings.

**10.c Service Announcements**  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out service related announcements. For instance, if our service is temporarily going to be down or suspended for maintenance, we might send our Customers a notification E-mail. Generally, Customers may not opt-out of these communications, however, if a Customer deactivates their account, service announcement E-mails are no longer sent to them. E-mail communications of this kind are not promotional in nature, and are delivered very far and few between, if they are sent at all.

**10.d Customer Service**  
We communicate with our Customers on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regard to issues relating to their account. We will generally reply via E-mail. These type of communications are sent in reply to a user's request for us to contact them.

### 11\. Information Sharing

**11.a Legal Disclaimer**  
We take every effort to preserve user and Customer privacy, however we will comply with disclosing personal information when required by law wherein such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order, or a legal process served upon us or on our Web site(s), in the event such disclosure is required to protect a person from harm.

**11.b Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)**  
We may share generic aggregated demographic information with our business affiliates and those looking to advertise with us, such as the amount of hits or visits to particular pages on our Web site(s) at any given time frame, solely for the purpose of showing value or evidencing the value of a certain ad spot that may be available for purchase by a third party. This does not link to or provide any personally identifiable information.

**11.c Third Party Links and Advertisers**  
With outside third party links located on our Web site(s), we endeavor to only link with reputable third parties (such as the Traffic Exchanges found in TEBrowser.com) for the purpose of supplying our Customers and users with useful information or "Quick-Links" to Web sites that are useful to any user wanting to surf the World Wide Web from our Web site(s). Other links you find on our Web site(s) will be targeting our own Internet advertisements and banner ads on this Web site, and on our other Web sites we link to, or to a third party advertisement. Some of these third parties may use cookies and clear GIFs on their Web sites, and if you visit their Web sites, those cookies and clear GIFs could load onto your computer allowing them to recognize a user when a user visits "our" Web site(s). Regardless of this kind of tracking some advertisers use on the Internet, the information they collect through this way with this technology is not personally identifiable, and is used by third parties and advertising agencies to track where their advertising budget is best placed for their own traffic/ad-cost ratio evaluations. For more information about any third-party advertisers or for the choices they provide you about not having this anonymous information used, please observe the Privacy Policies of any Web site you may reach from a link or advertisement on our Web site(s).

### 12\. Instances When You Share Your Personal Information

**12.a** We do NOT share your personal information with any third parties. However, if you fill in a form on or through a link you have found via an ad or link to a third party on our Web site(s), you will be initiating action to supply your information to that respective third party by your own free will. We are not responsible for information you submit outside of the Web site(s) and Web page(s) we own. The only avenues that are under our control where you are able to share your information with others is if you post your personal information to an advertising section on our Web site(s), or in the event you fill in and submit any of the following three (3) forms:

**1\. Third Party Merchant Account**  
We use an outside billing processing company to bill our Customers for goods and services. The Merchant Provider for our company is PayPal, who does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. To review PayPal's Privacy Policy please visit http://www.paypal.com.

**2\. Our Program**  
We associate with third party individuals with our TEBrowser Program. One of the specific services we provide our Members with is a free Web site for their marketing endeavors. These free Web sites may contain pages that link to forms that our Members advertise out on the Internet in hopes of having people and companies opt-in to receive information for them or to sign up for a product and/or service that will generate a commission fee to be paid to them for their sales. For example, when a user signs up for particular services, names, or other contact information like an E-mail address is necessary for the Member to provide information about products and services. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing information about products and services.

**3\. Business Transitions**  
In the event Webily, Ltd. goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, user, Customer, and Member personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

### 13\. Choice/Opt-out

**13.a** Our users are given the opportunity to opt-out of receiving information related to supplying more information about our products, services, and our Web site(s) on every communication sent. For example, our Company E-mails have an opt-out mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but do not want any marketing material, can keep their E-mail address off of our mailing lists.

**13.b** Users who have subscribed to our Newsletter who no longer wish to receive it, or any other promotional communications, may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the unsubscribe directions, which is located at the bottom of communications we send, or, the user may contact us through our "Contact Us" link in their Members Area Office directing us to remove them from our mailing lists.  
Users who have opted-in to receive information from our Independent Members may request removal from the Member's mailings at any time. We instruct all of our Members to provide an easy and prominent way for opting-out of their mailing lists, however, we do not monitor the E-mail sent by our Members, thus do not track which Members are including this easy opt-out option on their mailings. For further information and instruction on what to do if one or more of our Independent Members of our Program is not respecting your request for removal from their mailings, please read our "Anti-Spam Policy", Article 7.

### 14\. Links

**14.a** Our Web site(s) contain links to other Web sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other Web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Web site(s) and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by our Web site(s).

### 15\. Surveys And Contests

**15.a** From time-to-time, our Web site(s) and/or mailings may offer users surveys and contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose the information requested on the respective forms. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and E-mail address), and demographic information (such as state and zip code). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes, or if a respective contest is provided by a third party, contact information will need to be shared with the contest third party sponsor(s), however, we will indicate who the sponsor(s) is/are on any such contest forms. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of our Web site(s). A user's personally identifiable information collected in any and all surveys on our Web site(s) is not shared with any third parties. If we use an intermediary to conduct any surveys or contests, the intermediary party may not use any personally identifiable information for any other secondary purposes outside of the survey and/or contest we are conducting. For further information about Contests we provide, please see Article 22 below.

### 16\. Tell-A-Friend

**16.a** Webily may offer a Tell-A-Friend function. If a user elects to use a Tell-A-Friend referral service to inform a friend about a link or promotion on our Web site(s), we ask the Referrer for their name and E-mail address and the friend's name and E-mail address. In such an instance we will automatically send the Referrer's friend a one-time E-mail inviting them to visit a link or promotion that the Referrer is wanting them to see. We would only store this information for the sole purpose of sending the one-time E-mail and to track the success of a Tell-A-Friend program. In the event Webily offers such a program, the friend, or friends, that receive the one-time E-mail will be provided the name and E-mail address of the person who has Referred them, so they may contact the Referrer to either thank them for the information, or to request that they not refer them to a Tell-A-Friend type system again.

### 17\. Chat Rooms, Message Boards, and Public Forums

**17.a** Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on-line (for example on message boards, through E-mail, in chat areas, etc.) that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting any personal information on-line that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

### 18\. Security

**18.a** We take every precaution to protect all of our users' information. If a user submits sensitive information via our Web site(s), their information is protected both on-line and off-line.

**18.b** While on a secure page, the "lock icon" on the bottom of the Microsoft Internet Explorer Web browser becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just 'surfing'.

**18.c** We also do everything in our power to protect user information off-line. All of our users' information is restricted to our main office and is not accessible to anyone via any on-line channel. Only contracted employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, customer service and support) are granted access to this kind of personally identifiable information.

**18.d** ALL of our contracted employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices, and they are required to observe new policies when added, to ensure they are able to answer any and all question that may be asked by users. Our contracted employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy on a regular basis, and what they can do to ensure our users' information is protected.

**18.e** Finally, all of our servers, including the ones that store personally identifiable information, are in a completely secure environment.

### 19\. Supplementation of Information

**19.a** In order for our Web site to properly fulfill it's obligation to users, it may necessary for us to verify and/or supplement the information we receive with information from third party sources. The time we would outsource or seek interaction with a third party, who we classify as "Required Third Parties", to verify and/or supplement information with is summed up and described as follows:

**1\. IP Address Verification;** is monitored and logged to verify a user's identity on-line, which is collected via electronic means when opt-in forms and support applications are being filled in by a user, or when we need to ensure that it is in fact the accountholder we are communicating with via an on-line channel. When requests for personal identifiable information (such as password recovery, upgrading accounts, canceling accounts, etc.) are being discussed directly with accountholders, this is one of the avenues we use to insure accountholders are who they say they are. However, we may not always rely on IP Addresses solely for these processes, we may also require users to answer security questions to prove they are actually the accountholder.

**2\. Purchasing History;** is logged to do with the products and services accountholders have in their portfolio, which we keep updated by way of communication with our third party payment system provider. This is done in order for us to enhance our ability to tailor our Web site(s) to a user's preference. We may combine information about the purchasing habits of users from basic information our third party payment system provides when they report an approved transaction so we can create more of a personalized user profile to assist our accountholders. When a user makes a purchase from any of our Web sites, we may use both personal and demographic information in the construction of a profile.

**3\. Enhancement of Marketing Profile;** may be done to increase our database. We may purchase third party marketing data (such as targeted key-word traffic, home base business seeking leads, etc.) and add the users' information we obtain to our existing user database to better target our advertising and provide pertinent offers we think our users would be interested in. We also use this information to enhance or overlay the 'profile' of individual users. This type of marketing data may sometimes be directly tied to users' personally identifiable information.

### 20\. Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

**20.a** If a user's personally identifiable information changes, or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can also be done by contacting us through our Members area "Contact Us" link.

### 21\. Notification of Changes

**21.a** If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will usually post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and/or other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**21.b** If, however, we are going to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify users by posting a notice at the top of this Web page for 30 days. Changes to our Privacy Policy may be of a minor nature, on occasion, for which notification may or may not be provided other than such minor updates simply being added to, or taken away from, our Privacy Policy without notice.

### 22\. Entries in Contests, Draws, and Giveaways

**22.a** If you enter a contest, draw, or giveaway (referred to hereafter as "Contest") offered by Webily, Ltd. you will be providing us with personally identifiable information about yourself.

**22.b** By entering a Contest you are; (i) agreeing to provide registration information to Webily, Ltd, (ii) agreeing to provide registration information to a third party if we have involved a third party's product or service to be awarded, and (iii) agreeing to receive newsletters that may contain other offers, opportunities, products, and/or services from us and/or a third party if we have involved a third party's product or service to be awarded.

**22.c** Provided you take advantage of products and/or services offered on our Web pages or newsletter E-mails, or in later E-mail offers about a third party's products or services delivered by us, you authorize us to share your full registration information with any such third party for their use in their direct marketing to you if the products and/or services are owned and operated by a third party. All personally identifiable information that is submitted in connection with any Contest shall become the property of us and may be used by us in the future for marketing of products and services, or other purposes.

**22.d** Our forgoing privacy statement explains how we use your information, however, in the event we are involved with a third party in or on a Contest, information will be supplied about any such third party's privacy policy, and who, if anyone or another entity, they may share your private information with, and how they protect it, through a link to the respective third party's privacy policy. If you take advantage of marketing opportunities offered by any third party, your submitted personally identifiable information will also become the property of such third party, and we recommend that you review such third party's privacy policy to fully understand how they treat such information.

### 23\. Contact Information

**23.a** If you have questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our Contact Us link.

Last modified February 11, 2010.
